The West was never this far west.
Quigley Down Under is a western film directed by Simon Wincer.
American Matt Quigley answers Australian land baron Elliott Marston's ad
for a sharpshooter to kill the dingoes on his property.
But when Quigley finds out that Marston's real target is
the aborigines, Quigley hits the road.
Now, even American expatriate Crazy Cora can't keep Quigley safe in
his cat-and-mouse game with the homicidal Marston.
Matthew Quigley, played by Tom Selleck.
Crazy Cora, played by Laura San Giacomo.
Elliott Marston, played by Alan Rickman.
Major Ashley-Pitt, played by Chris Haywood.
Grimmelman, played by Ron Haddrick.
Dobkin, played by Tony Bonner.
Quigley Down Under is a 1990 Western genre film, directed by Simon Wincer and starring
Tom Selleck, Alan Rickman, and Laura San Giacomo, and set in Australia.
Although it opened to generally poor reviews, it has
since developed an enduring niche following.
The film explores themes of chase, indigenous australians,
australian outback, fremantle, australian western.